HABIB SEIFZADEH

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER with more than 15 years of hands-on experience in full SDLC of enterprise applications. Expert in object-oriented principles such as SOLID and design patterns as well as architectural styles like MVC. I also have an eye for details, good communication skills, and enthusiasm for facing new challenges.



CONTACT

habibseifzadeh@gmail.com

**** +61 413 024 423

Moncrieff, Canberra, ACT, Australia

@habibseifzadeh

in Habib Seifzadeh

SKILLS

Programming

PHP Java JavaScript Python

HTML/SCSS

Databases

MySQL Microsoft SQL SQLite

Frameworks and Methods

Laravel
Microsoft MVC
VueJS/Vuex

VueJS/Vuex Scrum

Cloud based Platforms

Amazon AWS Issue Tracking

(e.g., Azure Devops, Jira, Trello, ...)

0000

000

Operating Systems

Linux Windows

Software & Tools

IDEs (especially PhpStorm) PHPUnit XDebug Docker

Jenkins Git

Languages

English (Certified NAATI interpreter)

Persian

CERTIFICATES

- # LinkedIn top 5% of PHP programmers
- # LinkedIn top 15% of object-orientation

ABOUT ME

I am Habib, a developer and software engineer who, not only has extensive experience in IT industry, but is also always keen to update his knowledge by using state-of-the-art technologies on projects. I am able to deliver a wide range of products based on customers' needs, from fast-delivered Wordpress websites to high-quality ones using sophisticated frameworks and tools.

WORK HISTORY

April 2016 - Present

♀ IPCO Limited, Isfahan

Senior Software Engineer

Some developed websites: http://talayemahdi.ir, http://salamatdorin.ir, http://amanatsoft.ir

September 2005 - March 2016

Dade Varze Mabna Engineering Co.

Developer & Software Engineer

Isfahan

Some developed websites: http://dibabuilding.com.au, http://amanatit.com

EDUCATION

September 2003 - July 2006

♥ Najafabad, Isfahan

September 1999 - June 2003

Najafabad, Isfahan

Master of Software Enginnering

Bachelor of Software Enginnering

ACHIEVEMENTS, HONOURS AND AWARDS

- ◆ Developed a generic e-shop system, easily adaptable to new businesses with minimun code change (Have been sold to 5 different businesses)
- ₱ Developed REST APIs to make a VB6 legacy system to be useful again
- Successfully completed projects from Canada, Iceland and Australia
- Successfully led a team of researchers on a project for Isfahan Municipality (migrating their systems to open-source and realising major cost savings)
- ▼ Improved customer satisfaction by performance tuning of several systems
- Established continuous integration tools to reduce the deployment costs

GENERAL SKILLS

 Punctual
 Fan of new challenges
 Believe in synergy
 Swift learner

 Critical thinker
 Meticulous
 Tolerant
 Good Communication Skills

A DAY OVERVIEW

